(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
こよこよだよー！
It's Koyokoyu!
せーの！
Ready, set...!
極・夜・部屋！
Go-ku-yo-be!
#こより実験中 スタート！
#KoyoriExperimentInProgress Start!
こよは...
Koyo is...
ずなの...
Zuna's...
やったー！
I did it!
マヨネーズは飲み物です！
Mayonnaise is a drink!
こんこよ24時間完走！
KonKoyo 24h Finished!
ぷよテト大会準優勝
Puyo Teto Tournament Runner-up
ディスコードショッキング
Discord Shocking
こよ夏甲子園2023
Koyo Summer Koshien 2023
AIこより誕生
AI Koyori Birth
チャンネル登録100万人達成！ありがとう！
1 Million Subscribers Achieved! Thank you!
無敵の笑顔で荒らすメディア
A media-disrupting invincible smile
知りたいそうで潜むミステリア
A mysterious secret that makes people want to know
抜けてるどこさえ彼女のエリア
Even her flaws are within her area
完璧で嘘つきな君は
You, perfect and full of lies
天才的なアイドル様
Are a genius idol
今日何食べた？好きな本は？
What did you eat today? What's your favorite book?
遊びに行くならどこに行くの？
If you go out, where do you go?
何も食べてない、それは内緒
I haven't eaten anything, that's a secret
何を聴かれても のらりくらり
No matter what I'm asked, I dodge and weave
そう淡々と だけど燦々と
So indifferently, yet so brilliantly
見えて見えない蜜は蜜の味
Visible yet invisible, honey tastes like honey
あれもないないない これもないないない
Not that, no, no, nor this, no, no
好きなタイプは？相手は？さあ答えて
What's your type? Who is it? Come on, answer
誰かを好きになることなんて私分からなくてさ
I don't really know what it's like to love someone
嘘か本当か知り得ない
Whether it's a lie or the truth, I can't tell
そんな言葉にまた一人落ちる
Another person falls for those words
また好きにさせる
Making them love me again
誰もが目を奪われていく
Everyone is captivated by you
君は完璧で究極のアイドル
You are the perfect and ultimate idol
金輪際現れない
The likes of which will never appear again
一番...
The number one...
無敵の笑顔で荒らすメディア
Invincible smile disrupting the media
知りたいその秘密はミステリアス
Wanting to know that secret, it's mysterious
抜けてるとこさえ彼女のエリア
Even her flaws are part of her territory
完璧で嘘つきな君は
You, the perfect liar,
天才的なアイドル様
Are a genius idol
はいはいあの娘は特別です
Yes, yes, that girl is special
我々は端からおまけです
We were just accessories from the start
お星様の引き立て役Bです
Just a supporting role B to the star
全てがあの娘のお陰…なわけない
No way everything is thanks to her
洒落臭い 妬み嫉妬なんてない
How annoying, I'm not jealous or anything
わけがない これはネタじゃないからこそ許せない
No way, this isn't a joke, it's unforgivable
完璧じゃない 君じゃ許せない
You're not perfect, I can't forgive you
自分を許せない
I can't forgive myself
誰よりも強い君以外は認めない
I won't accept anyone but the strongest you
誰もが信じ崇めてる
Everyone believes and worships her
まさに最強で無敵のアイドル
Truly the strongest, invincible idol
弱点なんて見当たらない
Can't find a single weakness
一番星を宿している
Hosting the brightest star
弱いとこなんて見せちゃダメダメ
You can't show any weakness, no, no
知りたくないとこは見せずに
Without showing anything unwanted
唯一無二じゃなくちゃイヤイヤ
It has to be one and only, or I'll hate it
それこそ本物の愛
That's what true love is
得意の笑顔で沸かすメディア
Thrilling the media with her best smile
隠しきるこの秘密だけは
Only this secret remains hidden
「愛してる」って嘘で積むキャリア
Building a career on the lie "I love you"
これこそ私なりの愛だ
This is my own version of love
流れる汗も綺麗なアクア
Even the sweat is beautiful aqua
ルビーを隠したこの瞼
These eyelids that hide the ruby
歌い踊り舞う私はマリア
Singing and dancing, I am Mary
そう、嘘はとびきりの愛だ
Yes, lies are the ultimate love
誰かに愛されたことも
Being loved by someone
誰かのこと愛したことも
Loving someone else
ないそんな私の嘘が
My lies like that
いつか本当になること
Will one day come true
信じてる
I believe
いつかきっと全部手に入れる
One day I'll surely get it all
私はそう欲張りなアイドル
I'm such a greedy idol
等身大でみんなのこと
Just as I am, everyone
ちゃんと愛したいから
Because I want to love you properly
今日も嘘をつくの
I'll lie again today
この言葉がいつか本当になる日を願って
Wishing for the day these words come true
それでもまだ
Even so, still
君と君にだけは言えずにいたけど
I haven't been able to say it just to you
ああ、やっと言えた
Ah, I finally said it
これは絶対嘘じゃない
This is absolutely not a lie
愛してる
I love you
みんなー！ こんこよー！
Everyone! Kon-koyo!
博衣こより2周年記念ライブ、見に来てくれてありがとうございます！
Thank you for coming to see my 2nd Anniversary Live!
イェーイ！
Yay!
今回のテーマは「Memories & Future」！
The theme this time is "Memories & Future"!
たくさんの想い出を振り返りながら
While looking back on many memories,
3年目、未来へ向かっていくパワーを込めた
putting power into our 3rd year
ライブにしたいと思って作りました！
and the future, I created this live!
そして1曲目は、歌ってみたも出した
And for the 1st song, I sang and danced to "Idol",
「アイドル」を歌って踊らせていただきましたけれども
which I also released a cover of...
どうだったー？
How was it?
いやこの曲はもう
Well, this song...
歌もダンスもめちゃめちゃ難しい曲で
...is extremely difficult in both singing and dancing,
歌ってみたを出したのも結構挑戦な気持ちだったので
and releasing the cover felt like quite a challenge,
大切な1曲として歌いました！
so I sang it as a very important song!
おっ、可愛かった、かっこよかった、ありがとう！嬉しい！
Oh, "cute", "cool", thank you! I'm so happy!
それでは！ 続いては早速ゲストコーナーに行こうと思います！
Now then! Next, we'll head straight to the guest corner!
いろんな想い出を
We'll look back on various memories
新たに生まれたあの企画動画と共に振り返っていきますので
along with that newly created project video,
楽しんでください！
so please enjoy it!
それでは、どうぞ！
Without further ado, here you go!
せーの！
Ready, set...
はい！ はい！ はい！ はい！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
博衣こよりだよ！
It's Hakui Koyori!
はい！ はい！ はい！ はい！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
ホロライブの頭脳！
Hololive's brain!
頭脳はこよりです！
The brain is Koyori!
なんでも快解！ こよりちゃん
Everything Solved! Koyori-chan
あなたのアイドル
Your idol
サインはB！
The sign is B!
ちゅっ！
Chu!
うりゃ！ おい！ うりゃ！ おい！
Urya! Oi! Urya! Oi!
ようやく会えたね 嬉しいね
Finally we met, I'm so happy
待ち遠しくて足をバタバタしながら
I was so eager, kicking my feet...
今日を楽しみに
Looking forward to today,
眠れなかったよ
I couldn't sleep!
俺もー！
Me too!
緊張なんかしてる場合じゃない
This is no time to be nervous!
一分一秒無駄になんてできない
Can't waste a single second!
さあ、始めましょう
Now, let's begin!
君も 君も 君も
You too, you too, you too!
お待ち遠様
Thank you for waiting!
手を鳴らせ いらっしゃいませ
Clap your hands, welcome!
人が集まれば いよいよこそ
Once everyone's gathered, it's finally time!
日常はクロークの中
Leave your daily life in the cloakroom.
ここに来たなら踊らにゃ損損損
If you've come here, you've gotta dance!
サインはB！
The Sign is B!
ちゃんと見えてる　君のサイリウム
I can see them clearly, your glow sticks
今ふっと吹けば飛ぶような
Like something that would blow away with a puff...
小さな小さなサインだけど
...it's a tiny, tiny sign, but
私を推してくれるのなら
If you're going to support me
最大級のレスをあげる
I'll give you the biggest response
あなたのアイドル　サインはB
Your idol, the sign is B
チュッ！
Chu!
うりゃおい！うりゃおい！うりゃおい！うりゃおい！
Urya-oi! Urya-oi! Urya-oi! Urya-oi!
B小町！ フー！
B-Komachi! Hoo!
待たせたな　そりゃ当然　自己紹介
Sorry to keep you waiting, of course, it's introduction time
自慢してほしいよ　推しちゃいな
I want you to be proud, so go ahead and support me
誰でもない　君と君と　今を楽しむわけよ
It's no one else but you and you, I'm here to enjoy the moment with
引きこもりも　人見知りも
The shut-ins, the shy ones too
普段と違う顔見せてよ
Show me a side of you that's different from usual
みんな今日体調はどうだい？
How's everyone feeling today?
なりふり構わずに　サン・サン・サン！
Without a care for how you look, Sun, Sun, Sun!
独り笑われていても関係ない
It doesn't matter if you're laughed at for being alone
周りがどうとかこうとか気にしない
Don't care about what's going on around you
ちゃんと見えてる　君のサイリウム
I can see them clearly, your glow sticks
たとえ世界が私を拒んで
Even if the world rejects me
独りぼっちを感じたとしても
And even if I feel all alone
あなたが味方でいてくれたら
If you're by my side as an ally
怖いものはないよ
I have nothing to fear
見てよ　見てよ　何か始まる
Look, look, something's about to start
君との物語が
The story with you
なんて素晴らしい景色だ
What a wonderful view
昨日がいいか今がいいか関係ない
It doesn't matter if yesterday was better or today is
箱が大きい小さいとか気にしない
I don't care if the venue is big or small
ちゃんと見えてる　君のサイリウム
I can see them clearly, your glow sticks
今ふっと吹けば飛ぶような
Like something that would blow away with a puff...
小さな小さなサインだけど
...it's a tiny, tiny sign, but
私を推してくれるのなら
If you're going to support me
あなたが味方でいてくれたら
If you're by my side as an ally
最大級のレスをあげる
I'll give you the biggest response
あなたのアイドル　サインはB
Your idol, the sign is B
チュッ！
Chu!
うりゃおい！うりゃおい！うりゃおい！うりゃおい！　B小町！　フー！
Urya-oi! Urya-oi! Urya-oi! Urya-oi! B-Komachi! Hoo!
あまりにキュートでセンシティブ
So cute and sensitive
やべー
Whoa...
爆発で隠さなきゃ
Gotta hide it with an explosion
ぽよっとな
Poyotto-na
なんでもWAO!! 爆解!! こよりチャン
Nandemo WAO!! Bakuretsu!! Koyori-chan
我愛你　酔いが覚めない
Wǒ ài nǐ, the intoxication doesn't fade
Oh, I need you　恋が醒めない
Oh, I need you, my love won't awaken
お生憎様の慣れ果てさ　察して
The sorry end of a pitiful state, please understand
無問題　破滅してみて
Méi wèntí, try ruining yourself
Hold me tight　トラウマの味
Hold me tight, the taste of trauma
猛反対　お手お座りでハイ報酬
Strongly opposed, hand, sit, and here's your reward
喉の奥がチクンチクン
A sting in the back of my throat
僕はドクンドクン
My heart goes thump-thump
鼓動で孤独消してみてよ
Try to erase the loneliness with your heartbeat
愛も恋も独占して
Monopolize both love and affection
僕を独占して
Monopolize me
このまま中毒になるまで
Until we're addicted like this...
チューしよ
...let's kiss
そして Get get get on! Get get get on!
And then, Get get get on! Get get get on!
Get get get on chu!
熱く溶けるくらいに溢れた気持ちが
These feelings overflowing until they hotly melt
たまらないでしょ
You can't resist them, right?
Get get get on! Get get get on!
Get get get on chu!
我愛你　無問題
Wǒ ài nǐ, méi wèntí
Get get get on chu!
ポンチーカン　勝負はいつも
Pon, Chi, Kan, the match is always...
トンチンカン　僕に言わせりゃ
...absurd, if you ask me
ちんぷんかんぷんだ　最後はロンでしょ？
It's all gibberish, the end is 'Ron', right?
もう何回？
How many times?
殺されればいい
How many times must I be killed?
Oh, One night　忘れられない
Oh, One night, I can't forget
終わんない　トキメキ偏愛予報
It never ends, the heartbeat-fluttering bias forecast
喉の奥がチクンチクン
A sting in the back of my throat
僕はドクンドクン
My heart goes thump-thump
心臓ごと引きずり出してみてよ
Try dragging it out, heart and all
心臓ごと引き抜いて
Pulling out my heart along with it
きもちいい
It feels good
きもちいいね 面倒くさいけど
It feels good, though it's a bother
やっぱ照れくさいけど
It's still embarrassing, though
死ぬまで忘れられない
I won't be able to forget until I die
チューしよ
Let's kiss
いかれた街はゾンビで溢れる
The crazy town is overflowing with zombies
君は僕に恋してる
You are in love with me
ときめく胸に繋がるロープを
Pull the rope connected to my...
引きなよ
...heart that's thumping
いくよ
Here we go
Bet bet bet on Bet bet bet on Bet on chu!
本気で狂えるくらいの鬱々しさが
This gloominess that could drive me truly mad...
美しいでしょ
...is beautiful, isn't it?
Get get get on Get get get on Get on chu!
せーの ポンチーカン 終わんない
One, two... Pong, Chi, Kan! It never ends
Get get get get on chu!
ほらね
See?
我爱你
I love you
無問題
No problem
Get get get get on chu!
こより、どうぞ。
Koyori, here you go.
とても辛い調味料をたっぷり使った一品だよ！
It's a dish with plenty of very spicy seasonings!
やってないよ！
I'm not doing it!
電波テンポアップして 絶賛感電中！
Electric wave tempo up, currently being electrocuted!
あなたにもわすれたいこと かなしいこと
You probably have things you want to forget...
あるのかしらね
...sad things too
振らない映画なのに 涙をながすのは
Even though it's not a movie I'd reject, shedding tears...
ドラマチックが足りていないからよ
...is because there's not enough drama
そんな風に付かないこと くだらないこと
Not thinking that way, about trivial things...
考えてばかりね
...that's all you do
雨が上がれば 愛もその横顔も
Once the rain stops, love and that profile...
誰かのものになるのでしょう
...will probably belong to someone else
束の間のワンデーショーも全部 今夜はダメよ
The fleeting one-day show and all, not tonight
一体全体 如何して 如何して 何故 何故？
What on earth, how, how, why, why?
不安定な感度ら どこまでゆくの
Unstable sensitivity, how far will it go?
あなた一切合切 放り去ってもう
Throw everything away already
冗談じゃないわ
It's no joke
トウキョウ・シャンディ・ランデヴ
Tokyo Shandy Rendezvous
その時が来たって どうにもならないぜ
Even when the time comes, there's nothing that can be done
曖昧な本当なんて メランコリーがするだけ
Vague truths just make me feel melancholy
さあ掻っ攫って今テイクオンミー
Now, snatch me away and take on me
はあ ちゃんちゃらおかしなハトばかりで 食指がピクリともしないわ
Hah, just a bunch of ridiculous pigeons, I don't feel like lifting a finger
実態の無い感情 放っておいたって 策略なんてありゃせんのに何故
Even if you leave formless emotions alone, there's no strategy involved, so why?
ああもう懲り懲りよ
Ah, I've had enough
あたしの火となる気炎も じっと堪えてトリップ食らっては とうとう臨界点
Suppressing my fiery spirit, taking a trip, finally at the critical point
年中無休リップサービス 音沙汰かましてはへきえき
Year-round lip service, making some noise and being fed up
どんがらがっしゃん フィールガールは涙の目にモノ
Crashing and banging, the "feel girl" sees things through teary eyes
今や頭の中のミュージックのせいで あなたの話は一向に聞き取れない
Now, because of the music in my head, I can't hear a word you're saying
調子を待とうなこと言って yeah
Saying something sensible for once, yeah
回り出すダンステフル全部 忘れさせてよ
Let me forget all the rotating dance floors
だけど一体全体 如何して 如何して 何故 何故？
But what on earth, how, how, why, why?
不安定な感度ら 消えないまんまで
Unstable sensitivity, remaining without fading
あなた一個二個三個 食い違ってもう
One, two, three things being mismatched already
冗談じゃないわ
It's no joke
トウキョウ・シャンディ・ランデヴ
Tokyo Shandy Rendezvous
その時が来たって どうにもならないぜ
Even when the time comes, there's nothing that can be done
曖昧な本当なんて メランコリーがするだけ
Vague truths just make me feel melancholy
あたしを今
Me, right now
冗談じゃないわ
It's no joke
トウキョウ・シャンディ・ランデヴ
Tokyo Shandy Rendezvous
その時が来たって どうにもならないぜ
Even when the time comes, there's nothing that can be done
不甲斐ないね トゥナイト ランデヴーで落とすだけ
It's disappointing, isn't it? Just falling in tonight's rendezvous
あたしと足並み合ってイエロー・マジック
Keeping pace with me, Yellow Magic
アイアイアイ
Ai ai ai
トウキョウ・シャンディ・ランデヴ
Tokyo Shandy Rendezvous
その時が来たって どうにもならないぜ
Even when the time comes, there's nothing that can be done
曖昧な本当なんて メランコリーがするだけ
Vague truths just make me feel melancholy
さあ掻っ攫って今テイクオンミー
Now, snatch me away and take on me
ハロー×バイバイはいつもセット
Hello and goodbye are always a set
手を伸ばしたら遠ざかって
When I reach out my hand, it moves away
引き攣った顔を戻して モヤモヤ消化エンドレス
Fixing my cramped expression, an endless cycle of digesting haze
近付かれたら 離れたくなって
When people get close, I want to pull away
頼らなくても 平気なんです
I'm fine even without relying on anyone
ちょっと待って 誰も頷かない
Wait a minute, no one is nodding
これじゃお手上げ状態
This is a hopeless situation
笑顔作れば色めき立って
If I put on a smile, things liven up
きっと惹かれあうはずの法則
The law that says we should be attracted to each other
なんで？
Why?
響かない
It doesn't resonate
難解過ぎる愛の方程式
The equation of love is too complicated
焦って曖昧な答え出す必要はない
No need to rush and give a vague answer
理解できない性質だって
Even if it's a nature I can't understand
不安定も歓迎
I welcome the instability
片足で立って
Standing on one leg
アンバランスが
Unbalance is
僕の証明
my proof
笑えない
I can't smile
ぐちゃぐちゃな感情の正体？
The identity of these messy feelings?
拗れ上る後悔
Tangled regrets
真面目さ故馬鹿を見るってなに？
What does it mean to be a fool for being serious?
これじゃお手上げ状態
This is a hopeless situation
本当はそれほど強くないから
Because honestly, I'm not that strong
平気じゃない
I'm not okay
大丈夫じゃない
I'm not alright
なんで？
Why?
言えない
I can't say it
正解ない愛の方程式
The equation of love with no correct answer
振り回されて消耗してもナンセンス
It's nonsense to be jerked around and worn out
反発したいわけじゃない
It's not that I want to rebel
わかってるのに
Even though I know
肝心なとこで
at the crucial moment
アンバランスな
unbalanced
僕の性根
is my true nature
明快だ感情の実態
The reality of my feelings is clear
本当の愛知りたくて
I want to know true love
無理やりでも側にきて
Come to my side even if it's by force
難解過ぎる愛の方程式
The equation of love is too complicated
焦って曖昧な答え出す必要はない
No need to rush and give a vague answer
理解できない性質だって
Even if it's a nature I can't understand
不安定も歓迎
I welcome the instability
片足で立って
Standing on one leg
支えていてよ
Support me
僕の正体
My true identity
アンバランスが
Unbalance is
僕の証明
my proof
はーい！ということで
Alright! So...
ゲストとの曲3曲と、なんとここで初お披露目
after three songs with guests, I've just performed
新しいオリジナル曲を歌わせていただきました！
my brand-new original song for the first time!
どうだったーーー！？
How was it!?
えー、ゲストパートでは、こんこよ24やゲーム大会
In the guest part, people who have helped me in
コラボでお世話になった皆様にゲストにお越しいただきました
Kon-Koyo 24, game tournaments, and collabs came as guests.
ありがとうございました！
Thank you so much!
パフォーマンスしたかった曲を一緒に歌えてめちゃめちゃ嬉しかったです
I'm so happy I could sing songs I wanted to perform with them.
みんなもコメント、拍手とかで盛り上げてくれて本当ありがとう！
Thanks everyone for hyping things up with comments and applause!
そして、新オリジナル曲は「アンバランス」というタイトルです
And the title of the new original song is "Unbalance".
こちらも最近だとリコリコのオープニングの「ALIVE」などを手がけていらっしゃる
It was created by Shigenaga Ryosuke-san, who also worked on
重永亮介さんにお作りいただきました！
the LycoReco opening song "ALIVE" among others!
こより初の「恋」をテーマにした曲となっております！
It's my first song with the theme of "love"!
恋がよくわからない不器用な女の子の心情を
It coolly and emotionally depicts the feelings
エモくかっこよく仕上げましたので、後でじっくり歌詞も堪能してね！
of a clumsy girl who doesn't understand love well. Enjoy the lyrics later!
えー、この曲はですね、ライブ終了後にすぐMVがプレミア公開
The MV for this song will premiere right after the live,
24時からリリースされます！ぜひヘビロテしてください！
and it'll be released at 24:00! Please listen to it on repeat!
それでは、この後はソロ曲、そしてコラボパートを続けてお楽しみください
Now, please continue to enjoy the solo songs and the collaboration part.
では、次の曲の準備をします！
I'll get ready for the next song!
なんと、斬新な「ガチ恋距離準備タイム」！
Behold, the innovative "Gachikoi Distance Preparation Time"!
いぇーい！ふー！
Yay! Woo!
これをやってる間に準備がされちゃう...よし、準備万端！
The prep is happening while I'm doing this... Alright, I'm all set!
もう準備ができたみたい。ではいきましょう！
Looks like the preparations are done. Let's go!
だだだだだだだ、バーン！
Dadadadadada, bam!
ということで、聴いてください、「アルケミィ」！
With that, please listen to "Alchemy"!
Alchemy
無限に生きたい
I want to live forever
無限に生きられたら
If I could live forever
全て叶う
Everything would come true
でもいろんなものが
But so many things
あたしを追い込んでく
Are backing me into a corner
生きる残り時間
The time I have left to live
夢の座標 行方
The coordinates and location of my dreams
全部大事なものなのに
Even though they are all so important
いざ ここらでちょっと
Now, let's take a moment
甘いもの食べていこう
And go eat something sweet
そういう思考停止
That kind of mental paralysis
ばかり得意になった
Is the only thing I've gotten good at
歩いてきた道 振り返ると
When I look back at the path I've walked
嫌なことばかりで うんざりだよ
It's full of nothing but bad things, I'm fed up
触れるものを輝かせていく
To make everything I touch shine
そんな道を歩いてきたかったの
That's the kind of path I wanted to walk
無性に生きたい
I desperately want to live
焦ってばかりの日々
These days of nothing but impatience
全て消えそう
It feels like everything's about to disappear
でもサボってもみる
But I'll try slacking off too
だって疲れちゃうじゃない
Because I'll just get tired otherwise, right?
そんな矛盾思考
With such contradictory thoughts
あたし頭を振った
I shook my head
知らないうちに 眠ってたみたいだ
It seems I fell asleep without realizing it
いざ ここらでちょっと
Now, let's just
要領よく行こう
Go about this efficiently
ずっと起きていられる
Do you have any medicine
薬は置いてませんか
That can keep me awake forever?
ぼさっと立ってるだけでも
Even just standing around aimlessly
化石になってしまいそうなんだよ
I feel like I'm going to turn into a fossil
誰からも 忘れられたような
As if I've been forgotten by everyone
霞んだ存在になってしまうよ
I'm becoming a hazy existence
いざ ここらでちょっと
Now, right here, right now
根性見せてやる
I'll show you my guts
自分で頬叩いて
Slapping my own cheeks
存在の証明
Proof of my existence
歩いてきた道 振り返らない
I won't look back at the path I've walked
嫌なことばかりでも 前へ進め
Even if it's full of bad things, move forward
触れるものを輝かせていく
To make everything I touch shine
そんな存在になってみせるよ
I'll show you I can become that kind of being
みせるよ
I'll show you
ダイアモンド クレバス
Diamond Crevasse
神様に恋をしていた頃は
Back when I was in love with God
こんな別れが
I never thought
来るとは思ってなかったよ
A parting like this would come
もう二度と　触れられないなら
If I can never touch you again,
せめて最後に　もう一度抱きしめてほしかったよ
At least for the last time, I wanted you to hold me once more.
It's long long goodbye...
さよなら　さよなら　何度だって
Goodbye, goodbye, no matter how many times.
自分に夢中に言い聞かせて
I'll keep telling myself, absorbed in my own thoughts.
手を振るのは優しさだよね　今　強さが欲しい
Waving goodbye is a form of kindness, right? Now, I want strength.
あなたに出会い　星が輝いて　あたしは生まれて
I met you, the stars began to shine, and I was born.
愛すればこそ　iで爆走
Because I love you, I race through life with 'i'.
希望のない奇跡を待って　どうなるの
What will happen if I wait for a miracle without hope?
涙に滲む　星の瞬きは　ゴォ...
The twinkling stars, blurred by tears, are...
忘れないよ　あなたの温もりも　その優しさも
I won't forget your warmth, or your kindness.
すべて包んでくれた両手も
Or both of your hands that wrapped around everything.
Oh... It's long long goodbye...
さよなら　さよなら　愛しい人
Goodbye, goodbye, my beloved.
あなたがいたから　歩いてこれた
Because you were there, I was able to walk this far.
ひとりなんかじゃなかったよね　今　答えが欲しい
I wasn't alone, was I? Now, I want an answer.
燃えるような流星捕まえて　灯をともして
Catching a burning meteor, lighting a flame.
愛していたい　iさえ　果てて
I want to keep loving, even if 'i' reaches its end.
冷えた体　ひとつで世界は　どうなるの
With just one cold body, what will happen to the world?
張り続けけていた　虚勢が溶けてく
The bravado I kept putting on is starting to melt away.
Oh... どうしてなの　涙あふれて
Oh... why am I overflowing with tears?
止められない...
I can't stop it...
あなたに出会い　星が輝いて　あたしは生まれて
I met you, the stars began to shine, and I was born.
愛すればこそ　iで爆走
Because I love you, I race through life with 'i'.
希望のない奇跡を待って　どうなるの
What will happen if I wait for a miracle without hope?
涙に滲む　星の瞬きは...
The twinkling stars, blurred by tears...
生まれ変わって　また巡り会うなら
If we are reborn and meet again,
その時もきっと　あたしを見つけ出して
Then surely, find me again.
もう二度と　離さないで捕まえてて
Never let me go again, keep hold of me.
ひとりじゃないと　囁いてほしい　プラネット
I want you to whisper that I'm not alone, Planet.
こよちゃん、一緒に歌おう！
Koyo-chan, let's sing together!
ふぇ！？この曲を？いいんですか？
Eh?! This song? Is it okay?
ふぅわ〜！嬉しすぎてもう...
Fuwaa~! I'm so happy, I'm gonna...
爆発！
Explode!
こよちゃん！
Koyo-chan!
なんでも142解！こよりチャン
Everything Koyori Solved! Koyori-chan
息をしている
I am breathing
君は生きている
You are alive
当然のことだと
Thinking it's natural
誰も疑わないの
No one doubts it
息をしている
I am breathing
ように見えている
Or so it seems
生の裏側
The flip side of life
私にとっての何か
Is something to me
鼓動がドクドクしている
My heart is thumping
叩かれても腐らずに
Not rotting even if beaten
ここで歌うよ
I'll sing right here
ボタン一つの
A single button's
いのち
Life
最期まで私のこと覚えててくれるの？
Will you remember me until the end?
消えてしまいそうなの
I feel like I'm fading
分かってよ 分かってよ、ねぇ
Please understand, please understand
本当はどっちなの
Which is the truth?
恋と愛は違うんでしょ
Crushes and love are different, right?
君が忘れちゃったら
If you forget about me
私はいなくなるの
I will cease to exist
いのちのような夢を見ているよ
I'm dreaming a life-like dream
またねバイバイ
See you, bye-bye
息をしている
I am breathing
密かに生きている
Living in secret
自己証明を欲して
Longing for self-proof
欲しがっているんだ
I am longing for it
音が止まって
The sound stops
動かなくなって
And I stop moving
そんな私を
That version of me
君は笑ってくれるかな？
Will you smile for me?
鼓動がドクドクしている
My heart is thumping
嫌われても腐らずに
Not rotting even if hated
ここで歌うよ
I'll sing right here
気分次第の
Dependent on mood
いのち
Life
最期まで私のこと見届け続けてくれるの？
Will you keep watching over me until the end?
冷めてしまいそうなの
I feel like I'm going cold
分かってよ 分かってよ、ねぇ
Please understand, please understand
声が聞こえるんだよ
I can hear your voice
塩辛い涙が出ちゃうほど
So much that salty tears fall
君が忘れちゃったら
If you forget about me
私はいなくなるの
I will cease to exist
いのちのような夢を見ているよ
I'm dreaming a life-like dream
またねバイバイ
See you, bye-bye
ふさぎ込んだあの日を
That day I was feeling down
軽く弄らないで 止めて
Don't toy with it lightly, stop
それが生きる糧になるから
Because that becomes fuel for life
大丈夫、ずっと私は
It's okay, I will always
歌い続けるから
Keep on singing
さぁ 最期まで私は生きているか分からないけど
Now, I don't know if I'll be alive until the end
君がくれた言葉は
The words you gave me
確かに残ってる
Certainly remain
最期まで私のこと覚えててくれるの？
Will you remember me until the end?
満ち死んでしまうだろ
I'll probably die fulfilled
分かんない 分かんないよ、ねぇ
I don't know, I don't know
痛いくらい気持ちが
Our feelings sync up
シンクロする時もあるけど
To a painful degree sometimes
君が忘れちゃったら
If you forget about me
私はいなくなるの
I will cease to exist
いのちのような夢を見ているよ
I'm dreaming a life-like dream
またねバイバイ
See you, bye-bye
野球観戦楽しいですね！
Baseball games are fun, aren't they!
そうでしょ？
Right?
こよりもホームラン打ってみたいの！
Koyori wants to try hitting a home run too!
いーくよー！
Here I go!
これだー！
Take this!
やめろー！
Stop it!
背番号1のすごいやつが相手
My opponent is a great guy with number 1 on his back
フラミンゴみたいにひょいと一本足で
He stands on one leg like a flamingo
スーパースターのお出ましに
When the superstar makes his entrance
ベンチのサインは敬遠だけど
The sign from the bench is to walk him intentionally
逃げるのは嫌だわ
But I hate to run away
男ならここで逃げの一手だけど
If it were a man, he'd run away here
女にはそんなことはできはしない
But a woman can't do that
弱気なサインに首を振り
I shake my head at the timid sign
得意の魔球を投げ込むだけよ
And just throw my favorite magic ball
勝負よ 勝負よ
It's a showdown, a showdown
しんと静まった
The stadium went
スタジアム
completely silent
世紀の一瞬よ
It's the moment of the century
熱い勝負は
A hot match
恋の気分よ
feels like love
胸の鼓動がドキドキ
My heart is pounding
視線はクラクラ
My vision is dizzy
負けそう 負けそう
I'm about to lose, about to lose
私ピンクのサウスポー
I'm the pink southpaw
きりきり舞いよ
Spinning around
魔球は魔球は
The magic ball, the magic ball
ハリケーン
is a hurricane
背番号1のすごいやつが笑う
The great guy with number 1 laughs
お嬢ちゃん投げてみろとやつが笑う
He laughs, telling me to give it a shot
しばらくお色気サヨナラ
Farewell to charm for a while
デカい相手をしとめるまでは
Until I bring down that big opponent
ちょいとお預け
I'll put it on hold
さあとかけぬける
Now, it runs through
サスペンス
the suspense
スリルの瞬間よ
It's a moment of thrill
熱い視線が
The hot gaze
絡み合った
Intertwined
白い火花がパチパチ
White sparks crackle
心はメラメラ
My heart is burning
燃えそう 燃えそう
It's about to burn, about to burn
私ピンクのサウスポー
I'm the pink southpaw
きりきり舞いよ
Spinning around
魔球は魔球は
The magic ball, the magic ball
ハリケーン
is a hurricane
腕相撲大会で背中を押してくれた
ぺこら先輩にお礼がしたいの！
I want to thank Pekora-senpai for
supporting me at the arm wrestling tournament!
好きなもの、好きなもの...
Something she likes, something she likes...
爆発好きですよね！
You like explosions, don't you!
やめるぺこー！
Stop it, peko!
令和！
Reiwa!
この混沌とした令和のインターネットを
This chaotic Internet of the Reiwa era
照らす一筋の光
A single beam of light that shines
電子の海を漂うオタクに笑顔を
Bringing smiles to otaku drifting in the electronic sea
未来の平和をお約束
Promising peace for the future
躁鬱だけどまかせとけ
I'm manic-depressive, but leave it to me
インターネット・エンジェル、ただいま降臨！
Internet Angel, descending now!
社会を辞めろ
Quit society
家族を辞めろ
Quit your family
人間関係を辞めろ
Quit human relationships
今すぐ薄暗い部屋で青白いライトを浴びろ
Right now, bathe in the pale light in a dim room
大丈夫、怖かったこと全部上書きするからね
It's okay, I'll overwrite everything that was scary
現実よりも Crazy for you
More than reality, Crazy for you
おかしくなりそうなほど情報過多のインターネット
The Internet is so overloaded with information it makes you go crazy
今助けてあげるよ
I'll save you right now
ダーリン
Darling
ウソはウソであると見抜けるし
I can see through lies as lies
この愛は暴走しちゃうし
And this love is going out of control
壊れてしまうけど
Even if it breaks
考えなくていいんだよ
You don't have to think about anything
もうすぐ楽になるから
Because it'll be easy soon
脳内に乱反射する
Reflecting chaotically in my brain
poison radio
麻薬より甘いよ
It's sweeter than drugs
いいね　よくないね
Like it, not like it
キミにとっては毒だね
It's poison for you
いいね　よくないね
Like it, not like it
それでも飲むんだね
But you still drink it
いいね　よくないね
Like it, not like it
二人のヒミツだね
It's our secret
わたしだけ見ててね
Just keep your eyes on me
まるで天使のように微笑む
Smiling like an angel
強めの幻覚 INTERNET GIRL
A strong hallucination, INTERNET GIRL
そして悪魔みたいにささやく
And whispering like a devil
アナタだけのデパス NEEDY GIRL
Your very own Depas, NEEDY GIRL
浅い眠りと承認欲求のオーバードーズ
Shallow sleep and an overdose of desire for recognition
脳天直撃するわたしたちだけの宗教と光
The religion and light that strike our brains directly
倫理より激しく生きた宇宙すら侵食する恋
Love that lives more intensely than ethics and erodes even the universe
何度も送られる毒電波を優しさだけで包んで
Wrapping the poison waves sent over and over in only kindness
逆さまのコンピューターと断片的なカウンセリング
Upside-down computers and fragmentary counseling
きらめく屋上で奏でた夢見心地の旋律
The dreamy melody played on the sparkling rooftop
夕暮れ時にさよならの練習をして
Practicing saying goodbye at twilight
壊して 愛して 許して
Break me, love me, forgive me
狂って 狂って 狂って 甘く狂わせて
Go crazy, go crazy, go crazy, let me go crazy sweetly
ゆらぎ始める世界
The world begins to waver
曖昧になる風景
The scenery becomes ambiguous
アナタだけが映っているメモリ
The memory where only you are reflected
神様なんていないよ
There's no such thing as a God
このふざけたインターネットは七色のサイケデリック
This ridiculous internet is a seven-colored psychedelic
SNSという瓶詰め地獄に救済を
Salvation for the bottled hell called SNS
過去の歴史は見ないふり
Pretend not to see past history
アナタのためならすぐそばに
I'll be right by your side for you
インターネット・エンジェル可愛く参上
Internet Angel, making a cute appearance
まるで天使のように抱きつく
Clinging to you like an angel
強めの幻覚 INTERNET GIRL
A strong hallucination, INTERNET GIRL
そして悪魔みたいにキスする
And kissing like a devil
アナタだけの NEEDY GIRL
Your very own NEEDY GIRL
想い出から未来へ。
From memories to the future.
ここから始まる、3年目の第一歩！
Starting from here, the first step of the third year!
信じよう 仲間と一緒に
Let's believe, together with friends
挑戦ののろしをあげよう
Let's raise the signal fire of challenge
終わらない青春アーカイブ
An unending youth archive
恥じらい周知心捨てて Hey Jump
Discard your shyness and self-consciousness, Hey Jump
みんなで空へ羽来るジャンジャン
Everyone flock to the sky, jan-jan
ビタースウィート的なこぼれ落ちて
Bittersweet-like, spilling over
青春感じている 猛暑日
Feeling youth on a scorching day
成長した姿を見せたい
I want to show you how much I've grown
ビフォーアフター完璧 ほんまはもっと
The before-and-after is perfect, but honestly, I want more
全力でハイ！ハイ！ハイ！うー！
With all our might, Hai! Hai! Hai! Woo!
大切な想い出 たくさんあるけどね
There are many precious memories, but...
まだ感傷に浸ってる暇はない
There's no time to be sentimental yet
今世紀最大の高揚が始まる
The greatest excitement of this century begins
想像の果てにある高み
The heights at the edge of imagination
立ち止まった景色は尊い
The scenery we stopped to see is precious
逃げるな 限界の壁超えて
Don't run away, cross the wall of limits
僕らはまだチャレンジャー Yeah!
We're still challengers, Yeah!
冷たい声に溺れたって
Even if you drown in cold voices
微かな望み...
A faint hope...
...をたぐり寄せるように
...as if reeling it in
期待外れだと誰かが嘆く
Someone laments that it's disappointing
行きたいと痛いがいつも戦う
"I want to go" and "it hurts" are always at odds
プライドだけを頼りに抗う
Fighting back, relying only on pride
自分を信じたい
I want to believe in myself
努力は報われる
Effort will be rewarded
笑いたい奴は笑ってろ
Let those who want to laugh, laugh
感傷に浸ってる暇はない
I have no time to wallow in sentimentality
今世紀最大の
The greatest of this century...
今夜が始まる
...tonight begins!
Woah 反響が足りない もっともっと
Woah, the resonance isn't enough, more, more!
Woah
後悔はさせない
I won't let you regret it
Woah
想像の果てにある高み
The heights at the end of imagination
Woah
勝ち獲った景色は尊い
The scenery we won is precious
Woah
逃げるな 限界の壁超えて
Don't run away, cross the wall of limits
Woah
僕らはまだチャレンジャー
We're still challengers
(Yeah!)
Woah...
一緒に歌ってくださったゲストの皆さん、本当にありがとうございましたー！
To all the guests who sang with me, thank you so much!
それでは続いて、未来へと繋げていく、本日2曲目の新しいオリジナル曲です！
Now, moving on, here's the second new original song of the day, connecting us to the future!
なんと今回、こよ、初めて作詞に挑戦いたしました！
And for this one, I, Koyo, challenged myself with writing lyrics for the first time!
みんなへの応援ソングです。聴いてください、Tear-Gazer。
It's a support song for everyone. Please listen: Tear-Gazer.
涙越えてゆけ
Go beyond the tears
ほら ほら ほら
See, see, see
いっくよー！
Here we go!
ぽつり漏れた
A single sigh escaped
幸せが逃げちゃいそうで 吐いたため息
Fearful that happiness might slip away
ねえ 鏡の中
Hey, in the mirror
無理な笑顔に 唇 歪む
My lips twist into a forced smile
どうして 僕だけ うまくいかないのかな
Why is it that only I can't seem to make things work?
独りよがりだとわかってる
I know I'm being self-centered...
(わかるよ)
(I understand)
自信をなくして 崩れ落ちた時
When I lost confidence and crumbled
君の声がしたんだ
I heard your voice
精一杯 目一杯
With all my might, with everything I've got
矛盾だらけ迷路の中で
Inside this maze full of contradictions
等身大 手に未来の鍵を見つけ出せ
Just as you are, find the key to the future in your hand
No way どんな難題でも
No way, no matter how difficult the challenge
満身創痍で弾き返せ
Repel it even if you're battered and bruised
へこたれたって まだまだ前進
Even if you're discouraged, keep moving forward
3, 2, 1, Find high!
Go my way どこまでも
Go my way, to the ends of the earth
諦めない 諦めないからさ
Because I won't give up, I won't give up
涙越えてゆけ ほら ほら ほら
Go beyond the tears, see, see, see
そう 君の前で
That's right, in front of you...
笑ってみせる 強がりな僕だけど
...I'll show you my smile, even if I'm just acting tough
毛布の中一人で 涙流す日もある
There are days when I shed tears alone under the covers
孤独の戦士だ
I'm a lonely warrior
自分に正直な 「やりたい」に真っ直ぐな
Honest with myself, true to what I "want to do"
君だけの頻度でありたい
I want to be at a frequency just for you
(最高！)
(Awesome!)
悔しさを重ねて 駆け上がっていこう
Accumulating regrets, let's keep climbing up
ねえ 今はまだ道の途中
Hey, we're still in the middle of the journey
きっと
Surely...
絶対諦めない
I'll never give up
ガンバってること 知ってるよ
I know how hard you're working
涙の理由も 知ってるよ
I know the reason for your tears, too
…だって君は僕と同じ
...Because you are the same as me
いつだってチャレンジャー
Always a challenger
突き抜けろ 夢の向こうまで
Break through to the other side of dreams
道に迷ったら 僕の声を聞いて
If you get lost, listen to my voice
精いっぱい
With all my might
めいっぱい 君と僕で重ね合わせて
To the fullest, combining you and me
等身大のU&D 泥だらけでも立ち上がって
Life-sized U&D, even covered in mud, stand up
がむしゃらでありのままで 理屈を超えて見返すんだ
Recklessly and just as you are, go beyond logic
力合わせて いざ行こう
Combining our strength, let's go now
精いっぱい
With all my might
めいっぱい まだまだ明日を目指して
To the fullest, still aiming for tomorrow
全力で
With all my power
U&D まだまだ夢の向こうへ
U&D, further still to the other side of dreams
No way どんな難題でも
No way, no matter how difficult the problem
Best Answerで弾き返せ
Repel it with the Best Answer
へこたれたって最後まで前進
Even if discouraged, advance until the end
C'mon! 1 2 5! High!
Blow My Tears どこまでも
Blow My Tears, wherever we go
僕たちは諦めないからさ
Because we will never give up
涙越えて行こう ほら、ほら、ほら、今、今
Let's go beyond the tears! Look, look, now, now!
3 2 1 Go!
僕だけじゃない
It's not just me
君だけじゃない
It's not just you
博衣こより2周年ライブ、見てくれてありがとう！
Thank you for watching my 2nd anniversary live!
ゲストさんとのプチトークがエンディングロールでありますので、
There's a short talk with the guests in the credits,
チャンネルはこのままでお願いします！
so please stay tuned to this channel!
ゲストの皆様に大きな拍手！
A big round of applause for all the guests!
そしてここで、大切なお知らせです！
And now, for an important announcement!
1曲目のオリジナル曲「アンバランス」はこのあとMVがプレミア公開！
The MV for 'Unbalance' will premiere after this!
24時から各種配信サイトでリリースされます。いっぱい聴いてね！
It hits streaming sites at midnight. Listen a lot!
そして2曲目の「Tear-Gazer」は瀬尾祥太郎さんに作曲・共同作詞していただきました。
And 'Tear-Gazer' was composed/co-written by Shintaro Saisho.
こちらは来週12月6日の0時にリリースされるので、絶対ゲットしてください！
It releases next week on Dec 6th at midnight!
さあお待たせ、2周年記念グッズの紹介です！
Now, let's look at the 2nd anniversary merchandise!
今回は、ついに出ます！ももこママ描き下ろしの「おっぱいマウスパッド」！
Finally, an 'Oppai Mousepad' drawn by Momoko-mama!
照れ顔が可愛すぎ！大きさは、どうなるんだろう、いかに？
The blushing face is too cute! How big is it?
おっぱいがあったら下半身も欲しいよね！ということで、「しっぽクッション」発売！
You want the lower half too, right? So, a tail cushion!
ふわもち素材で抱きしめて寝たらめちゃめちゃ気持ちいいよ！
It's so soft and squishy, it feels great to hug!
さらに！新衣装のグッズ欲しいよね！ということで、
Also! You want goods for the new outfit, right?
むーらん先生描き下ろしのめちゃかわアクリルキーホルダーもご用意しました！
We have cute acrylic keyholders by Muran-sensei!
なぜかマヨネーズの着ぐるみを着ているこよも。マヨラーも要チェックです！
Koyo in a mayo suit too! Mayo lovers, check it out!
シチュエーションボイス「しっぽのおはなし」も発売！
Situation voice 'A Tale of the Tail' is out too!
こよがいつも触っちゃダメって言ってるしっぽをついに…！そして、フルセットもございます！
The tail you're usually not allowed to touch...!
特典はポストカードとASMRボイス「ドキドキハプニングのおはなし」。
Bonus: postcard & ASMR 'A Heart-Pounding Incident'.
数量限定で直筆サイン入りもありますよ！絶対ゲットしてくださいね！
Limited handwritten signed versions are available!
2周年記念グッズはこのあと22時から発売！
Anniversary goods go on sale at 10 PM tonight!
使う用、保存用、布教用、何でもゲットだ！
One for use, one for storage, get them all!
このあとメンバーシップ限定アンコールライブもあります！
Membership-exclusive encore live is coming up!
3年目のこよも止まらねぇぞで頑張るので応援よろしくお願いします！
I'll keep going full speed in year 3, so support me!
助手くん、大好きだぞ！ん〜まっ！ばいばーい！
Assistants, I love you! *Mwah!* Bye-bye!
こよちゃん、2周年おめでとう！
Koyo-chan, happy 2nd anniversary!
ありがとうございます、アキ・ローゼンタール！
Thank you, Aki Rosenthal!
こんこよ24で頭脳を見せつけてくださったお二人です！
These two showed off their brains in Konkoyo 24!
なんか1位とっちゃって申し訳ないというか、自分なんかやっちゃいました？
I feel bad for taking 1st place... Did I do something?
まあ早慶卒だから当たり前だよね！
Well, you're a Waseda/Keio grad, so it's natural!
まあまあ、ホロライブの頭脳はアキロゼだからね！
Now now, the brain of Hololive is Akirose!
いや！頭脳は渡しませんからね！
No! I'm not handing over the 'brains' title!
こよりちゃん、2周年おめでとう！
Koyori-chan, happy 2nd anniversary!
Congratulations!
Oh, thank you!
こより！
Koyori!
Happy 2nd Anniversary!
Oh, thank you!
Thank you for asking to meet Koyori
when you came to Japan.
I was very happy!
I wish you have amazing year
that ends with accomplishing all
the great goals that you have set.
And I wish you were happy,
because I believe
not just me, but everyone probably know
that you bring happiness to everyone
and you really, really hard work
on every project that you have done.
I wish you be happy,
full of happiness, fun and cheer,
and I wish success in all you do.
Happy Anniversary Koyori-chan!
Love you!
こよちゃん、2周年おめでとう！
Koyo-chan, happy 2nd anniversary!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much!
AZKi先輩とライブで歌うのが夢だったんですが、
It was my dream to sing live with AZKi-senpai,
この場を借りて夢を叶えさせていただけちゃいました。
and I was able to make that dream come true here.
本当？
Really?
めちゃくちゃ嬉しいです。
I'm so happy.
前からこよちゃんの歌枠でも歌ってもらったりとか、
You've sung it in your karaoke streams before,
それこそ二人で歌枠コラボした時にも歌ったりね。
and we even sang it during our karaoke collab.
AZKiも大事にしているこの曲を、
This song is very important to me too,
今日一緒にこよちゃんと歌えてよかったです。
and I'm glad I could sing it with Koyo-chan today.
今日はゲスト呼んでくれてありがとう。
Thank you for inviting me as a guest today.
また一緒に歌いましょう。
Let's sing together again.
こよー、2周年おめでとう！
Koyo, happy 2nd anniversary!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much!
野球も連れて行ってくださって本当にありがとうございました。
Thank you so much for taking us to the baseball game.
めちゃめちゃ楽しかったです。
It was so much fun.
よかったー。
I'm glad.
またみんなでどっか遊びに行こうね。
Let's all go out somewhere together again.
やったー！行く行くー！
Yay! Let's go, let's go!
こより、2周年おめでとう！
Koyori, happy 2nd anniversary!
ありがとうございます、ぺこら先輩！
Thank you, Pekora-senpai!
なんで呼んでくれたん？
Why did you invite me?
実は、もう2年にもなるので白状するんですけど、
Actually, since it's been 2 years, I have a confession,
ぺこら先輩のこと、大好きなんです！
Pekora-senpai, I love you!
知ってるし。
I know.
え、何でですか？
Wait, why?
こよりが誰にでも大好きって言ってるの。
Because you say you love everyone.
違います！こよりは本当はぺこら先輩の憧れで大好きで...
No! Pekora-senpai is someone I look up to and love...
なので、振り練の時に「こより真似していいよ」って
That's why when you told me "You can copy me" during practice,
私に言ってくれたの本当に嬉しかったんです！
I was so happy!
本当？
Really?
じゃあこれからもよろしくね、こより。
Well, looking forward to working with you, Koyori.
こちらこそよろぺこです！
Likewise! Yoro-peko!
2周年ありがとう！！
今日という日を迎えられたのは、
助手くんの応援のおかげだよ。
「楽しい」も「嬉しい」も「悔しい」も
全ての想い出を糧に3年目へ！！
明日からもずっと一緒にいたいな。大好きだよ♡
Koyori 2023.11.28 博衣こより
Thank you for the 2nd anniversary!!
I was able to reach this day
thanks to all the assistants' support.
Taking "fun", "happy", and even "frustrating"
memories as fuel, onto the 3rd year!!
I want to be with you forever starting tomorrow. I love you♡
Koyori 2023.11.28 Hakui Koyori